"Happy birthday, dear Tommy,
"happy birthday to you."
And...
Wait, Tommy...
Birthday greetings first.
Okay.
Tommy, Tommy, my dear son,
you're 12 now,
so joyful and fun.
Time has passed
and years gone by,
but you'll always be
my pumpkin pie.
Dad...
I'm not done.
The candles might not outlast
the speech, so maybe...
I'll put it in your room.
Great!
Okay, moving on. Ready?
Wait! Make a wish.
Okay.
Okay, done.
What was it?
To blow out the candles.
Surprise!
Lasers?
Lasers! Lasers?
Mom, Dad, you're the best!
That's so cool!
Tommy... I'm sorry,
I have a situation at work.
A wedding cake fell. I have
to bake a new one right away.
Okay, you can go. Mom's here.
The thing is...
It's three layers of fondant
coated with gold powder...
I have to help Dad.
It's okay!
Daniel and I will watch the kids.
Right. Wait, what?
Great. We'll be back
as soon as possible.
Congratulations.
Bye, kids. Bye.
Enjoy.
Tommy...
Okay, ready?
Yes!
A few points before we begin.
What?
In this game we use
infrared laser technology.
You're probably asking yourselves
what this means. Not really.
Well, the laser emits a strong,
narrow beam of light,
one wavelength long.
Infrared light is a kind of
electromagnetic radia... Daniel.
Ready?
Ready for what?
Let's go!
There are safety rules!
Adi, cover me!
Tommy!
Tommy, are you okay?
Move! Tommy. Tommy...
Anna, the activity
was recorder here, on the right.
Noah, I see something. Pull over.
We have to report this to Eric.
Bye, see you!
Bye.
Wow, Nikki, that was awesome!
Happy birthday, little brother.
Now what?
Now we clean up.
What's that?
What is it?
No way!
Tommy, you cracked the glass!
I did? When?
Earlier, when you did
a whole show and hit the glass.
Tommy, why do you always
exaggerate everything?
It's called theatre, Nikki.
It's art. Wait, move.
Tommy, get me a mop.
Okay.
What's that?
What's going on here?
Let's check it out.
For the record,
I'm really against this idea.
Coming?
Again, for the record,
I think it's a mistake.
Are you coming or not?
What is this place?
Why didn't they tell us about this?
What are these glasses?
Guys...
why would Mom and Dad
need eight passports?
We've been suspecting that
someone's drying Lake Solomon.
Today we finally found out how.
Based on body type, it's a woman.
And what is this substance?
It's EX9,
an experimental substance
used for drying swamps
and treating floods.
The company that makes EX9
is Techno Sec Ltd.
The inventor is the CEO,
Emmanuel Goodman.
What do we know about this man?
Emmanuel Goodman...
Emmanuel Goodman, 43 years old,
CEO of Techno Sec Ltd
for the past ten years,
a qualified hydraulic engineer...
Lives near Lake Solomon,
where his wife, Naomi,
runs a guesthouse.
I just sent you the file.
Who is this man?
Hmm?
I want you to book a room
and go there tomorrow morning.
We must gather evidence,
see what he's up to,
who he works with.
Keep in mind you'll have
to be there for a while.
What about the kids?
We'll bring them along.
It's the perfect cover,
no one would suspect us.
No. Bad idea going with kids.
They can be quite nosy.
Don't worry, Eric.
Our kids aren't nosy at all.
What are you doing?
Trying to guess the password.
Nikki, you can't just
enter passwords. It might...
What do you think, Tommy?
Mom's birthday?
I strongly suggest
not to try and just
randomly guess. No way!
Try their anniversary.
I'm sure. Try it.
Okay, their anniversary.
It's her birthday, I'm sure.
You were sure before,
and it didn't work.
You need to learn to listen.
It's her birthday. Go for it.
Mom's birthday.
This will end badly...
Note it for the record.
Noted!
It's not a standard operation.
Having the kids with you 24/7
can be a problem.
With all due respect, Eric,
we've been in this business
for eighteen years,
and we never had a problem.
Except for last year.
How could I know
that woman had a wig?
Listen, if you type
the wrong password three times,
the computer will shut down!
It has to be Tommy's birthday!
My birthday! Of course! Okay.
A security breach in the system.
It's coming from
your computer at home.
I really hate being right...
Okay, you're right, I love it.
But for the record,
I warned you the computer
would lock down.
Daniel, you do realize
nobody actually takes notes, right?
I told you
not to type the password!
Okay, fine. You're right.
What a mess...
Anyone who knows anything
about computers, can do that...
Daniel, you're a genius!
Okay, let's tidy up so they
won't know we were here.
Ouch!
I can use this
to glue back the fish tank!
Okay, hurry! There's no time!
Nikki, wait.
Cleaning up won't help.
I'm sure they will get
a security alert
that someone hacked their computer.
Let's try to fix it.
I don't know...
Maybe install a software.
Like there was a malfunction.
Where's the mouse?
There's no mouse,
just a keyboard.
Great idea, Nikki!
Huh?
Mouse.
See?
There was a mouse here,
and these are its droppings.
That's what set off the alarm.
Nice!
I hope no one broke
into our command center.
Hi, kids. We're home!
Quickly!
Sit down, hurry!
Pretend you're bored...
The wig!
So, I'll explain it again,
Daniel. You see...
Offside is passing to a player
who's behind the defense.
Hi!
Hi.
How many times
do I have to tell you?
He's a real genius,
but when it comes to soccer...
It's really complicated...
So, Tommy, how was it?
Fun.
Great. Great...
So, Mom...
Looking for something? Great...
I asked if you're looking
for something. What?
Did you have fun, Tommy?
Yeah, it was awesome.
Good, that's good.
How about you?
Did everything work out
with the cake?
Cake?
The cake...
The cake!
Sure, the bride was thrilled.
Yes.
And...
We have a little surprise for you.
We had no time to tell you
about it because of...
The cake!
Right, the cake! Anyway...
To celebrate Tommy's birthday...
We're taking you on vacation
to a guesthouse by Lake Solomon!
We'll spend the entire
summer there!
Isn't that great?
Wow! Sun... So nice...
Heat... Yeah, awesome.
Mosquitoes...
Thanks...
That's good but I can't come,
I'm sorry.
I have soccer practice
and I can't be out of shape...
And I've got the audition
at the end of the summer...
But thanks.
I'm supposed to go on
a date with Zoe! Really?
She knows who you are?
I'm still working on it. Soon.
Listen, we checked everything.
Nikki, you can do
water sports in the lake,
it's really good exercise.
And Tommy, there's drama class.
You can practice for your audition.
It could be great for you!
What about Daniel?
The only thing I care about is...
Broadband internet!
When do we leave?
Tomorrow morning!
What fun!
Wow!
Noah, let's get ready! What fun!
Family time! Let's get ready!
That was weird.
But... it could be fun, right?
And it has been a while
since we went on vacation.
Unless it's not really a vacation...
False alarm, Eric.
It's just a mouse that got
into the command center.
I'll set a couple of traps
so it won't happen again.
Anyway, we're going ahead
as planned.
Okay, we're here.
Kiddos, you'll unload the bicycles?
Yes.
Tommy, be careful with my drone.
What?
A message from Eric.
Goodman is about to leave
for an important meeting.
Okay. You know what to do.
Of course. Hi there...
Be nice to them.
Hello.
Hi, nice to meet you. Hello!
Hi.
Hello!
Welcome to Lake Supreme!
I'm Naomi,
and these are my kids.
Hi, I'm Sean.
And that's my sister, Ella.
I'm Anna, and this is Noah,
and these are our kids,
Nikki, Tommy and Daniel.
Hello!
Cuties...
I apologize that my husband
isn't here to help you.
He has a back problem. Don't ask.
But shall we do a tour
of the guesthouse? Sure.
Anna, you go,
I'll finish unloading here.
Okay, this way.
I told you it's a normal vacation.
So, you must be the Fishers?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Emmanuel Goodman.
Hello, Emmanuel Goodman.
Noah Fisher, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
A beautiful place you've got here!
I'm sorry, but I have to run.
I have
a chiropractor appointment.
Enjoy your stay with us.
Thanks very much.
No one with a stiff back
looks like that...
I'm sure Mom and Dad
are here because of him.
Let's follow him!
I'm in. Huh?
Nikki? Tommy?
Hurry up!
Nikki! Nikki!
Daniel, come on!
We're like actual spies!
We just need a cool name...
Spyders! Because spies
are like spiders and...
Okay, I'll...
I'll meet you in ten minutes.
Make sure you're not
being followed.
He's going to meet someone!
I hope you're not going
to follow him. What?
Why? What's if it's important?
Tommy!
What if Mom and Dad need this
for their investigation?
Nikki, what do we do?
Daniel, get the drone.
Come on, hurry,
we can't lose him!
Daniel, you see him
on the screen?
I can't see a thing.
I have sweat in my eyes.
Hurry up! We can't lose him!
Come on, Daniel!
I'm sure it's nearby.
I'm beat!
Come on!
There he is! Come on!
Where the trail ends!
There they are!
I hope no one followed you here.
Don't worry. I checked a few times.
Remember, it's crucial
that this shipment
reaches its destination safely,
and without anyone knowing.
Your shipment is in good hands.
Let's begin.
We better film them
to show Mom and Dad.
Great idea.
I should have thought of that.
So film them!
Why me?
Because your mobile
is full of apps! It's hightech!
I can't see a thing.
I'll try to get closer.
Keep quiet.
Shh...
So much noise! Like an elephant
walking on nachos!
Hey, look. There's a heart.
I wonder who S and D are.
Okay, it's not working.
Let's use the drone.
Come on, that's such a...
Great idea, Nikki!
I should have thought
of that too.
But we have to mute it.
It makes too much noise.
Who, Daniel?
I've been saying that for years!
Not Daniel! The drone!
Oh... Oh! That's easy.
You got some sunscreen? Sure.
Which one? SPF 45 or SPF 98?
Do you know these numbers mean...
Daniel, not now!
Here.
Get down.
Try it now.
Zoom in, so we can see them.
A little to the right,
I can't see a thing.
It's a bit complicated. Wait...
No! He's about to sneeze.
Do it quietly!
Don't get stuck now...
It's stuck.
Someone has to climb up
and get the drone.
I would do it myself...
But Nikki is already climbing...
Can I help you?